

Daniel Piechota DevQA Specialist

sorry, hit my DMs

daniel.pi3chota@gmail.com 🔀

Warsaw, Poland

piechotadaniel.com

linkedin.com/in/danielpiechota/

About Me

Experienced game developer with more then a year of valuable adventure, driven to explore new horizons in the gaming industry. My work is characterized by a methodical detail-oriented approach, actively opportunities for continuous improvement.

Interpersonally, I am open-minded, approachable, and value constructive criticism. I approach every project with a blend of passion and responsibility, striving for excellence in all endeavors.

Education

Technical High School 2015-2019 Computer Science in Lubliniec

Skills

- Over 20 years of active gaming experience
- Over 2 years of competing at professional level in Battle Royale genre winning more than \$6.200 and accumulated total of \$10.000 revenue in gaming
- Out of box understanding of game mechanics in terms of reproducing and utilizing in proper environment leading to minmaxing
- Practical and theoretical experience in all game genres
- Methodical and adaptive problem solving
- Coming up with suggestions on what to modify or improve in terms of game design, level design and other aspects
- Creating feedback on game difficulty, scaling, progression and the end game
- Trouble-free adaptation to constantly changing ingame environments, characters and weapons meta
- Adaptive learning required skills to overtake new duties
- English at proficient level (C1), both spoken and written, actively attending courses

Work Experience

03.2023 - Present DevQA Specialist



- Working in Unreal Engine 5 Editor modifying Gameplay Abilities, Data Tables and troubleshooting skills in form of balancing perspective
- Responsibility of balancing Gameplay Ability System
- Delivered personal endless runner game project
- Responsibility of leading internal team meetings, preparing notes, collecting improvements proposals, striving for established high-level goals and reporting results to lead
- Experience in the early-stage development of a project, their phases and its life cycle
- Knowledge of progression systems, game mechanics, tools and their functionality
- Investigating progression systems and sharing their states by providing list of bugs and not implemented features
- Providing feedback on game modes for balancing and replayability effort
- Delegated to help with VR effort for Bulletstorm VR; feedback and game balance
- Working on designing and researching proposals for weapons and abilities

05.2022 - 03.2023 Junior Balance Tester



- Co-designing Outriders Worldslayer post-launch balance changes
- Limit testing builds to provide more data for easier balance effort
- Reading and putting into practice telemetry data
- Preparing feedback on weapons and gameplay
- Creating R&D documentations of modern techs for future projects
- Approaching game from the end-user perspective

Hobbies

- Video games
- Vast form of physical activities
- Competitive gaming, e-sport
- Cognitive science
- Technological innovations
- Streaming